<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Cameron Crites&#39; sports blog</title>
    <link>http://cameroncrites.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Cameron Crites&#39; sports blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://cameroncrites.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Who is the Best Goal Scorer in the NHL?</title>
      <link>http://cameroncrites.github.io/2022/04/19/who-is-the-best-goal-scorer-in-the-nhl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cameroncrites.github.io/2022/04/19/who-is-the-best-goal-scorer-in-the-nhl/</guid>
      <description>Over the course of the last few years, the National Hockey League has been blessed with some incredible talent, and with incredible talent, comes debate.
One common debate in every major sports league is the question of, “Who is the Best Player?” and thankfully, there is not much of a disagreement for NHL fans on who that is.
Connor McDavid. It wouldn’t take much research and debate to convince a common hockey fan that McDavid is the best of the bunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Nikola Jokic should win NBA MVP</title>
      <link>http://cameroncrites.github.io/2022/03/31/why-nikola-jokic-should-win-nba-mvp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cameroncrites.github.io/2022/03/31/why-nikola-jokic-should-win-nba-mvp/</guid>
      <description>When watching the NBA, there are multiple players that many fans go out of their way to watch on a nightly basis. Lebron James is arguably the greatest to ever play, Stephen Curry changed the game with his shooting ability, and Giannis Antetokounmpo looks to become the next face of the NBA after winning his first championship last season.
But any invested NBA fan will tell you there is another player that continues to change the way people look at the game.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
